webbrain.com 2019-12-10

# TheBrain Privacy Policy

### TheBrain Technologies Privacy Policy

#### We respect your privacy

Our goal is to protect your privacy while providing you information about our products and services that you want to have. We will disclose to you the types of information we gather and how we use it, then let you decide what personal information you want to share with us for particular purposes. In short, at TheBrain, you can control the ways in which your information is used or not used.

#### What information do we gather about you?

We gather information you voluntarily provide whenever you download or purchase a product directly from TheBrain, request information about our company or products or submit a request for customer support. The information we collect varies according to the circumstances presented. For example, if you decide to purchase a product from us online, we also will collect certain financial information from you, such as your credit card number, credit card expiration date, and billing address. If you simply request information from TheBrain by e-mail, we will ask you only for your e-mail address. You may also provide us your name and other information, at your discretion. In addition, our site uses cookies to keep track of your use and to enhance your experience on our site. Cookies are bits of data that are stored on your computer, not on our website.

#### How is this information used?

The way in which we use your information also varies depending on the circumstances presented. For example, we use your name, credit card information and e-mail address to process your orders for our products. We also use your customer information to alert you about product upgrades and revisions, to keep you posted on the status of your order or request and to respond to your questions about our products and services.

We may make your information available to qualified distributors of TheBrain technology who can better serve you or your geographic area. We require all such distributors to comply with applicable privacy laws and regulations.

#### Marketing

We use "remarketing" to enable third-party vendors, such as Google, display relevant ads from us on external web sites. These vendors use cookies to serve ads based on past visits to our web site. If you wish to opt out of Google's use of cookies, you can do so by visiting [Google's Ad Preferences Manager](https://www.google.com/ads/preferences/).

#### Security

The security of our visitors’ and customers’ data is a top priority at TheBrain. TheBrain uses state of the art technology to protect your data from use, misuse or alteration by unauthorized third parties. Currently, TheBrain uses Secure Socket Layer software (SSL) to protect your data and secure your transactions. SSL encrypts all your personal information, including your credit card number, name and address as it is transmitted over the Internet. Of course, we cannot guarantee the security of your Internet transmissions, and TheBrain does not warrant that your information will be absolutely secure. Any transmission of data on or through the use of TheBrain site is therefore at your own risk.

To ensure the highest level of protection of the information you disclose to TheBrain, we recommend that you not disclose any sensitive personal information about yourself to TheBrain.

#### What choices do you have about how your information is used?

We respect your privacy and realize that you may not like to receive promotional offers or unsolicited information. To ensure you receive only communications of interest to you, you may

  * Choose not to receive any communications from TheBrain, except where necessary to fulfill your order for our products or services; and
  * Control whether you are contacted with promotional material from TheBrain.
  * In addition, in the event TheBrain informs you that we intend to share your information with other companies, we will enable you to remove your name and information from our database. 

#### For more information

If you would like any additional information about TheBrain, this Privacy Policy or any of the products or services offered on this Web site, please contact [info@thebrain.com](mailto:info@thebrain.com) or write to us at TheBrain Technologies, 11522 W. Washington Blvd. Los Angeles, CA 90066. 

This Privacy Policy is incorporated into and subject to the terms of TheBrain Terms of Use Agreement
